Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Index: H4-01. Intramural Relations - University of California Policies re Students & Student Organization - Use of University Facilities & Non-Discrimination - UC Policies Applying to Campus Activities., 1978-1994. (Box 602, Folder 1)
- Index: H7-02. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - Campus Facilities Coordinating Commission., 1982-1985. (Box 602, Folder 10)
- Index: H7-01. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - Activity Guidelines., 1979-1983. (Box 602, Folder 11)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - (Extra Curricular Use of University Facilities)., 1976-1982. (Box 602, Folder 12)
- Index: H7-02. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - Campus Facilities Coordinating Commission., 1971-1981. (Box 602, Folder 13)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - (Institute of Historical Review)., 1981. (Box 602, Folder 14)
- Index: H7-01. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - Activity Guidelines., 1972-1979. (Box 602, Folder 15)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - (Franchan ISDS Appeal)., 1972-1974. (Box 602, Folder 16)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - (Report of Judicial Review Committee)., 1972. (Box 602, Folder 17)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities, Registered Organization & Use of University Facilities., 1977-1971. (Box 602, Folder 18)
- Index: H4. Intramural Relations - University of California Policies re Students & Student Organization, Use of University Facilities & Non-Discrimination., 1970-1973. (Box 602, Folder 2)
- Index: H4-01. Intramural Relations - University of California Policies re Students & Student Organization - Use of University Facilities & Non-Discrimination - UC Policies Applying to Campus Activities., 1970-1977. (Box 602, Folder 3)
- Index: H4-01. Intramural Relations - University of California Policies re Students & Student Organization - Use of University Facilities & Non-Discrimination - UC Policies Applying to Campus Activities., 1977-1978. (Box 602, Folder 4)
- Index: H7-02. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities, Registered Organization & Use of University Facilities - Campus facilities Coordinating Commission., 1989-1997. (Box 602, Folder 5)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities, Registered Organization & Use of University Facilities., 1979-1994. (Box 602, Folder 6)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities, Registered Organization & Use of University Facilities - Policy Manual., 1991. (Box 602, Folder 7)
- Index: H7. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities, Registered Organizations & Use of University Facilities., 1988-1989. (Box 602, Folder 8)
- Index: H7-02. Intramural Relations - Regulations & Procedures - UCLA Regulations, Activities - Campus Facilities Coordinating Commission., 1986-1988. (Box 602, Folder 9)
- Index: HA40. Intramural Relations - Student Disruptions & Discipline - Campus Discipline - Individual Disruptions (Public Relations Letters) A-H., 1970. (Box 603, Folder 1)
- Index: RF27. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium., 1982-1987. (Box 603, Folder 10)
- Index: RF27-02. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium - Lease Negotiation with Rose Bowl., 1978-1985. (Box 603, Folder 11)
- Index: RF27-01. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activates - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium - Transportation & Parking at Rosebowl., 1982. (Box 603, Folder 12)
- Index: VD4/U5. Instructional Units - GSEIS - Instruction & Research Activities - University Elementary School., 1976-1994. (Box 603, Folder 13)
- Index: VD4/U5. Instructional Units - GSEIS - Instruction & Research Activities - University Elementary School., 1976-1988. (Box 603, Folder 14)
- Index: VD4/U5. Instructional Units - GSEIS - Instruction & Research Activities - University Elementary School., 1972-1983. (Box 603, Folder 15)
- Index: VD4/U5. Instructional Units - GSEIS - Instruction & Research Activities - University Elementary School., 1970-1976. (Box 603, Folder 16)
- Index: VD4/U5L3. Instructional Units - GSEIS - Instructional & Research Activities - University Elementary School - Lab for Study & Impro Childhood Youth Education., 1979-1986. (Box 603, Folder 17)
- Index: VD4/U5L3. Instructional Units - GSEIS - Instructional & Research Activities - University Elementary School - Lab for Study & Impro Childhood Youth Education., 1976-1979. (Box 603, Folder 18)
- Index: VE4/H3. Instructional Units - Henry Samueli School of Engineering & Applied Science - Instructional & Research Activities - Hazardous Substance Control., 1984-1990. (Box 603, Folder 19)
- Index: HA40. Intramural Relations - Student Disruptions & Discipline - Campus Discipline - Individual Disruptions (Public Relations Letters) I-Z., 1970. (Box 603, Folder 2)
- Index: IB25. Public Relations - Cooperation, Aid & Information for Outside Entities - School and School Districts., 1986-1996. (Box 603, Folder 3)
- Index: RF27. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium - Handicapped Seating., 1982-1997. (Box 603, Folder 4)
- Index: RF27-05. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium - Rosebowl Operating Committee., 1992-1996. (Box 603, Folder 5)
- Index: RF27-01. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium - Transportation & Parking at Rosebowl., 1983-1995. (Box 603, Folder 6)
- Index: RF27. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium., 1982-1995. (Box 603, Folder 7)
- Index: RF27. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium - Alcohol., 1984-1994. (Box 603, Folder 8)
- Index: RF27-02. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Activities - Rose Bowl Stadium Home Football Stadium - Lease Negotiations with Rose Bowl., 1987-1994. (Box 603, Folder 9)
- Index: BB33/H3-04. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action- Discrimination Basic of Handicap-Americans w/Disabilites Act of 1990., 1992-1996. (Box 604, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - (Section 503 Employment of Handicapped Disabled)., 1976-1986. (Box 604, Folder 10)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - (Section 504 Discrimination Basis of Handicap)., 1978-1979. (Box 604, Folder 11)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - (ACR 201)., 1977-1979. (Box 604, Folder 12)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handi. - (Section 504 Non Discrimination Basis of Handicap)., 1977-1978. (Box 604, Folder 13)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - (Section 504 Non Discrimination Basis Handicap)., 1976-1977. (Box 604, Folder 14)
- Index: BB33/P8. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration Affirmative Action - Public Relations - (Code Previously BB33/I)., 1995-1996. (Box 604, Folder 15)
- Index: BB33/P8. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Public Relations., 1972-1995. (Box 604, Folder 16)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Handicap., 1977-1996. (Box 604, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action- Discrimination Basis of Handicap-Preventive Rehabilitation Program., 1979-1994. (Box 604, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - (OCR Investigation Discrimination Complaint)., 1987-1992. (Box 604, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/H3-04. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration-Affirmative Action- Discrimination Basis of Handicap-Americans w/Disabilities Act of 1990., 1991-1992. (Box 604, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/H3-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - Report to Legislature Re: Handicapped Access., 1986-1992. (Box 604, Folder 6)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Discrimination on the Basis of Handicap., 1976-1991. (Box 604, Folder 7)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - (ORC Investigation of Discrimination Complaint)., 1986-1987. (Box 604, Folder 8)
- Index: BB33/H3. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Affirmative Action - Discrimination Basis of Handicap - (Services to Students with Disabilities)., 1986. (Box 604, Folder 9)
- Index: BR10. Universitywide Administration & Academic Senate - Extended Academic & Public Service Programs-Western Center for Continuing Education in Hospital., 1973. (Box 605, Folder 1)
- Index: EA93/R4. Campus Management - Finance Accounting - General - Recharges., 1979-1995. (Box 605, Folder 10)
- Index: EA93/R4-03. Campus Management - Finance Accounting - General - Recharges - Policy., 1985-1994. (Box 605, Folder 11)
- Index: EA93/R4-02. Campus Management - Finance Accounting - General - Recharges - Administrative Recharges., 1990-1994. (Box 605, Folder 12)
- Index: EA93/R4-02. Campus Management - Finance Accounting - General - Recharges - Administrative Recharges., 1983-1990. (Box 605, Folder 13)
- Index: EA93/R4. Campus Management - Finance Accounting - General - Recharges - (Authorities & Duties of Recharge Committee)., 1971-1985. (Box 605, Folder 14)
- Index: EA93/R4-02. Campus Management - Finance Accounting - General - Recharges - Administrative Recharges., 1978-1982. (Box 605, Folder 15)
- Index: EA96/A8. Campus Management - Accounting - Administration & Staffing - External Audits., 1978-1983. (Box 605, Folder 16)
- Index: EA96/A8. Campus Management - Accounting - Administration & Staffing - External Audits - (Audit of Contracts & Grants)., 1976-1980. (Box 605, Folder 17)
- Index: EA96/A8. Campus Management - Accounting - Administration & Staffing - External Audits - (Audit by State Auditor General)., 1978-1980. (Box 605, Folder 18)
- Index: EA96/A8. Campus Management - Accounting - Administration & Staffing - External Audits., 1961-1978. (Box 605, Folder 19)
- Index: BT1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - General., 1972-1996. (Box 605, Folder 2)
- Index: EA96/A8. Campus Management - Accounting - Administration & Staffing - External Audits - (Audit by State Auditor General)., 1977-1978. (Box 605, Folder 20)
- Index: BT10. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - Internal Communication., 1972-1996. (Box 605, Folder 3)
- Index: BT10. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - Internal Communication - Weekly Heads up Bulletin., 1994-1995. (Box 605, Folder 4)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division of Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - North Village Plan., 1980-1986. (Box 605, Folder 5)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division of Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - Student Housing., 1978-1981. (Box 605, Folder 6)
- Index: E0.5/A25. Campus Management - General - Academic Personnel Records., 1977-1989. (Box 605, Folder 7)
- Index: E0.5/A25. Campus Management - General - Academic Personnel Records., 1976-1977. (Box 605, Folder 8)
- Index: E0.5/A25. Campus Management - General - Academic Personnel Records - Confidentiality of Faculty Peer Reviews., 1990-1994. (Box 605, Folder 9)
- Index: EG7-04. Campus Management - Parking - Construction & Financing - Parking Structure 4 Expansion., 1996-1997. (Box 606, Folder 1)
- Index: FB13. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Safety., 1973-1994. (Box 606, Folder 10)
- Index: FB13. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Safety., 1971-1991. (Box 606, Folder 11)
- Index: FB13-01. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Campus Lighting., 1976-1990. (Box 606, Folder 12)
- Index: FB13. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Safety., 1968-1985. (Box 606, Folder 13)
- Index: K49 (A-C). Extramural Support - Private Sources., 1978-1997. (Box 606, Folder 14)
- Index: K49 (D). Extramural Support - Private Sources., 1971-1997. (Box 606, Folder 15)
- Index: K49 (E-J). Extramural Support - Private Sources., 1965-1997. (Box 606, Folder 16)
- Index: K49-H. Extramural Support - Private Sources - (Hewlett)., 1994-1996. (Folder 17)
- Index: K49-K-02. Extramural Support - Private Sources - Keck Foundation., 1983-1997. (Box 606, Folder 18)
- Index: K49 (K-N). Extramural Support - Private Sources., 1989-1997. (Box 606, Folder 19)
- Index: EG7. Campus Management - Parking - Construction & Financing., 1978-1996. (Box 606, Folder 2)
- Index: K49-P. Extramural Support - Private Sources - (Pew)., 1989-1997. (Box 606, Folder 20)
- Index: EG7-01. Campus Management - Parking - Construction & Financing - Parking Structure 3 Expansion., 1988-1994. (Box 606, Folder 3)
- Index: EG7. Campus Management - Parking - Construction & Financing - (Lot 32)., 1981-1992. (Box 606, Folder 4)
- Index: EG7-03. Campus Management - Parking - Construction & Financing - VA Surface Parking Lot., 1986-1988. (Box 606, Folder 5)
- Index: FB7. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Disaster Preparedness & Recovery., 1993-1997. (Box 606, Folder 6)
- Index: FB7. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Disaster Preparedness & Recovery - (UCLA Emergency Plan)., 1970-1996. (Box 606, Folder 7)
- Index: FB7-02. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Disaster Preparedness & Recovery - Fire Protection., 1971-1987. (Box 606, Folder 8)
- Index: FB7. Plant Development & Maintenance - Environmental Health & Safety Office - Disaster Preparedness & Recovery., 1972-1986. (Box 606, Folder 9)
- Index: K49 (R-S). Extramural Support - Private Sources., 1970-1997. (Box 607, Folder 1)
- Index: S1. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - General., 1977-1990. (Box 607, Folder 10)
- Index: S4. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Administration & Staff., 1980-1985. (Box 607, Folder 11)
- Index: S19/C4. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Service & Operations Office - Service - Charter Flights., 1970-1996. (Box 607, Folder 12)
- Index: S52. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Educational Policy Commission., 1970-1988. (Box 607, Folder 13)
- Index: SA1. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association., 1978-1996. (Box 607, Folder 14)
- Index: SA1. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Students Association (GSA)., 1991-1992. (Box 607, Folder 15)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Students Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1990-1991. (Box 607, Folder 16)
- Index: SA1. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Students Association., 1985-1990. (Box 607, Folder 17)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Students Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1989-1990. (Box 607, Folder 18)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Association - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Students Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1988-1989. (Box 607, Folder 19)
- Index: K49-S-04. Extramural Support - Private Sources - (Spencer Foundation)., 1971-1997. (Box 607, Folder 2)
- Index: K49-T. Extramural Support - Private Sources - (TRW Axisymmetric Mirror Experiment)., 1984-1985. (Box 607, Folder 3)
- Index: NA4. Academic Personnel - Recruitment., 1982-1997. (Box 607, Folder 4)
- Index: NA4-01. Academic Personnel - Recruitment - R&R Survey., 1983-1996. (Box 607, Folder 5)
- Index: NA4. Academic Personnel - Recruitment - (Ladder Rank Faculty Diversity Statistic)., 1996. (Folder 6)
- Index: NA4. Academic Personnel - Recruitment., 1971-1991. (Box 607, Folder 7)
- Index: NA4. Academic Personnel - Recruitment., 1967-1978. (Box 607, Folder 8)
- Index: NA4. Academic Personnel - Recruitment - (Nepotism)., 1959-1971. (Box 607, Folder 9)
- Index: SA31. Student Associations - Ethic Students Associations - MECHA., 1970-1989. (Box 608, Folder 1)
- Index: SA40. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Other ASUCLA Organizations., 1971-1995. (Box 608, Folder 10)
- Index: U:0.5. Instruction General - (General Education)., 1985-1997. (Box 608, Folder 11)
- Index: U:0.5. Instruction General., 1973-1985. (Box 608, Folder 12)
- Index: U:0.5. Instruction General - (General Education)., 1980-1985. (Folder 13)
- Index: VE4/H3. Instructional Units - Henry Samueli School of Engineering & Applied Sciences-Instructional Research Activities-Hazardous Substance Control,NSFResearch., 1980-1990. (Box 608, Folder 14)
- Index: VE4/H3. Instructional Units - Henry Samueli School of Engineering & Applied Sciences-Instructional Research Activities-Hazardous Substance Control,NSFResearch., 1989-1990. (Box 608, Folder 15)
- Index: VE4/H3. Instructional Units - Henry Samueli School of Engineering & Applied Sciences-Instructional Research Activities-Hazardous Substance Control,NSFResearch., 1985-1989. (Box 608, Folder 16)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1988. (Box 608, Folder 2)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1987-1988. (Box 608, Folder 3)
- Index: SA1. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association - (Constitution)., 1977-1987. (Box 608, Folder 4)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1986-1987. (Box 608, Folder 5)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1985-1986. (Box 608, Folder 6)
- Index: SA1-01. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association - GSA Forum Meetings., 1985. (Box 608, Folder 7)
- Index: SA1. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association., 1975-1980. (Box 608, Folder 8)
- Index: SA1. Student Associations - Associated Students, UCLA - Graduate Student Association., 1970-1978. (Box 608, Folder 9)
- Index: BG1/G6. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Research Policy - Universitywide Research - Research Programs - Institute on Global Conflict and Coopera., 1981-1997. (Box 609, Folder 1)
- Index: E10. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements., 1984-1994. (Box 609, Folder 10)
- Index: E10. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements., 1980-1985. (Box 609, Folder 11)
- Index: E10. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements., 1972-1979. (Box 609, Folder 12)
- Index: E10/P6. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements - Policy., 1974-1976. (Box 609, Folder 13)
- Index: E10/P6. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements - Policy., 1971-1992. (Box 609, Folder 14)
- Index: E10/P6-01. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements - Policy - Independent Consultant Agreements., 1990-1997. (Box 609, Folder 15)
- Index: E10/P6-01. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements - Policy - Independent Consultant Agreement., 1979-1989. (Box 609, Folder 16)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use - (1985 World Games for the Deaf)., 1981-1983. (Box 609, Folder 17)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use (Gymnastics)., 1982-1983. (Box 609, Folder 18)
- Index: BB37-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Staff Personnel - Management Initiatives Group., 1992-1993. (Box 609, Folder 2)
- Index: BB37-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Staff Personnel - Management Initiatives Group., 1993-1994. (Box 609, Folder 3)
- Index: BB37-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Staff Personnel - Management Initiatives Group., 1994-1995. (Box 609, Folder 4)
- Index: BB37-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Staff Personnel - Management Initiatives Group., 1985-1996. (Box 609, Folder 5)
- Index: E10. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements - (Contract Commitment Study)., 1979. (Box 609, Folder 6)
- Index: E10. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements., 1979-1980. (Box 609, Folder 7)
- Index: E10. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements - (Oil and Gas)., 1977-1979. (Box 609, Folder 8)
- Index: E10. Campus Management - Business Services - Leases & License Agreements - (Oil and Gas)., 1980-1982. (Box 609, Folder 9)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use., 1978-1984. (Box 610, Folder 1)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use., 1986-1989. (Box 610, Folder 10)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use - (Presidential Debate)., 1988-1992. (Box 610, Folder 11)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use., 1983-1994. (Box 610, Folder 12)
- Index: JB19-02. Governmental Relations - California - Legislative Branch - Assembly - California Breast Cancer research Council., 1993-1997. (Box 610, Folder 13)
- Index: K4. Extramural Support - Administration & Staff - (Media Matters)., 1973-1974. (Box 610, Folder 14)
- Index: K4. Extramural Support - Administration & Staff - (Evaluation)., 1975. (Box 610, Folder 15)
- Index: K4. Extramural Support - Administration & Staff., 1972-1976. (Box 610, Folder 16)
- Index: K$. Extramural Support - Administration & Staff., 1983-1996. (Box 610, Folder 17)
- Index: K4-01. Extramural Support - Administration and Staff - Overhead funds., 1971-1972. (Box 610, Folder 18)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use., 1979-1985. (Box 610, Folder 2)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use - (Gymnastics)., 1983-1986. (Box 610, Folder 3)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use - (1985 World Games for the Deaf)., 1984-1986. (Box 610, Folder 4)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use., 1983-1987. (Box 610, Folder 5)
- Index: ID23. Public Relations - Use of Campus - Facilities - Request to Use - (World Veteran Games 1989)., 1986-1987. (Box 610, Folder 6)